[Music]
we need a better a long way to go
yeah oh yeah but guess where we'll
listen to the FML right here on Spotify
let's see how far the salt legs ways
asking if we're still going to Salt Lake
City
I'm always the passenger bros
the copilot path
we didn't take over to change lanes we
didn't disengage it was just a game
change lanes ourselves you cannot switch
lanes with the home you just yeah so we
got ways Spotify
my driver got 32 Skokie's out there
oh wow I don't know if this scope is
still happening today - people like
school try a new one in every eye grows
grows
gopro's people want us to go 100 miles
per hour that's against the law
yeah we SAT here though coalition it up
go 85 that's cool there's not much in
the van
the batter Nevada
righto
you
sweat shirts for sale no white buddies
are not for sale
we got Woody's 1:29 I know I said
yesterday the t-shirts were $20 but I
lied we looked at how much little peep
was selling his t-shirts Laurent to her
and it was 30 yeah
so considering that this is me living
out my dream of being like little peep
their turn they never and you can blame
lope you should write a letter to his
estate does everyone have an estate no
only if you're the kind of person who
gets assassinated you get murdered you
don't have to stay here we assassinated
Rimmer
yeah a little we've got some minds about
that by the way I'm not loving this
album
yeah can you make a common little piece
of collab shirt oh I'd have to get a
little keeps of states yeah we got a
call it's we protect intellectual
property we respect intellectual
property promise but only cuz we're in
America that's right if we was in China
or my own sovereign country yeah would
strike Bo okama low Windex oh that
that's bad so up or achievable you know
I might know some frozen no little
Windex yeah might be a video full Windex
shout me out where is that video
how many parts will people be able to
try on this tour Oh trying cars on the
tour just I've grabbed that wish to see
you guys yeah we'll see many people are
there if it's only a few yeah you guys
could try the car yeah so don't tell
your from home but if it's like 200 like
we might be getting at some of these
places then look at the car yeah look
that we'll see we'll see we only have
this car with us now
what you think we're like a convoy and
we program the other car service plus
you just fill it up with merch yeah
look let's give this song a try
yeah vanilla guerrillas bringing the
civet Oh
oh man
[Music]
sort of you what a few right
good shot
show them out check these out
like stalactites was that in campus what
is the mouse will town
you want to go to your campus yo we got
we got four wheel job we go off-road it
does look
go on the internet check facebook yeah
look at more social forum
so wait shrugs
[Music]
south care of him car yeah you guys this
is actually the freezing
go let's go alright let's listen to
oh my god or is it the fact that I was
using to modify
he knows it's no one will know this all
we didn't check if the ER muster up
today
oh man this one M&M was good
yeah when was this we use this to down
yeah like just listen to the tape all
right
we both through matters why all the fuss
about
[Music]
this was good go wait for the ICP dish
that's line in the song good
old-fashioned passionate asshole can you
shoes coat you had took him
since my coloring book still help is it
still hot the gay these domains
Oh case this shot is beautiful what this
shot is beautiful
this music is beautiful
it's broken kind of
look at how beautiful this is though if
you guys again bear me that one now the
ITC they're associating this track on
Lemaitre damn right to the meanest I'm
their - Marley - well oh we should
this is the miracle holy lost service
love to wait for miracles yes
oh wait but the scope is can't be
watching this anyway maybe t-mobile them
your attorney Fred Nixon's a but
now the label was afraid that Fred
Gibson would sue W yeah the attorney
yeah holy moly so is the label there no
one needs a labeling the label also
censor his line about the kids of
Columbine
ah miracles okay
it shouldn't say no sim where's no
service
I kind of wanted to return the EON a few
times but now you're happy we're just
five bug reports yes
my great previous role in its early
there's no simian mode
Wow Miranda Lambert and my stud or what
comes up when you start to tighten
barrels
No
an ICP not on Spotify there we go how's
your work on binocular slam doing well I
have to remember not to cover the camera
music oh yes
yes
I really want to go to like a juggle
[Music]
way too far
change leads automatically but you can't
change without disengaging yeah
for an hour I always house it
yep must be like
well it'll be cooler when you stop to
watch yeah
nice
beautiful
all right maybe we leave the parrot see
what this year was next time you see at
Utah you Utah